<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Milestone on The Quartermaster project.</title>
    <link>http://qmstr.org/tags/milestone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Milestone on The Quartermaster project.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://qmstr.org/tags/milestone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quartermaster Milestone 1 Development Report: Voilà, a modular, extendable FOSS Compliance Toolchain</title>
      <link>http://qmstr.org/blog/2018/04/25/qmstr-milestone-1-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://qmstr.org/blog/2018/04/25/qmstr-milestone-1-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Version 0.1 is here. After a proof-of-concept, plenty of drafting,
feedback and discussions, a prototype, and finally three months of
development focused on creating a useful product, we are tagging a
first version of Quartermaster. The theme of the first version was to
implement the toolchain basics: the compliance knowledge graph, the
master container, the elemental workflow with a construction, analysis
and reporting phase, and the APIs for modules to interact with the
knowledge graph in each of these phases. There are public showcases
that demonstrate the functionality implemented so far. After gathering
functional and legal requirements, the team will now move on to
milestone 2, where we will focus on making use of the building blocks
from the first version to implement badly needed functions of
generating license compliance documentation - an SPDX manifest
analyzer, integration with Fossology, and features to aggregate
analysis results from different sources into reports.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>